<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
  <template id="term_and_conditions">
  <t t-set="choreo_fs" t-value="'font-size:6pt;'"/>
    <t t-set="choreo_style_p"
      t-value="'font-style:normal;font-weight:normal;margin-top: 1px;margin-bottom: 5px;'+choreo_fs" />
    <t t-set="choreo_style_p_title"
      t-value="'font-style:normal;font-weight:bold;'+choreo_fs" />
    <t t-set="choreo_style_p_title_2"
      t-value="'font-style:italic;font-weight:bold;'+choreo_fs" />
    <t t-set="choreo_br" t-value="'margin-top: 2px;margin-bottom: 2px;'" />
    <div class="row" style="page-break-before: always! important; width:100%; marin-top:0px">
      <div style="width: 33.33%; padding: 10px;">
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">GENERAL
          TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF BUSINESS</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">1. Object of the Contract</div>
        <div
          t-att-style="choreo_style_p">This document constitutes the General Terms and Conditions of
          Business of choreograph which shall apply to all direct marketing Services offered by the
          company choreograph (hereinafter referred to as "choreograph"), SAS a company with a
          capital of 397 313 euros, registered in Lille Trade and Companies Register under number
          489 496 331 and headquartered at 27 bis, rue du Vieux Faubourg, 59000 LILLE (FRANCE).<br /><br />choreograph
          uses information and data provided by data providers in order to build and improve shared
          databases of which choreograph is both the author, within the meaning of article L112-3 et
          seq. of the French Intellectual Property Code, and the producer within the meaning of
          article L341-1 et seq. of the same Code.<br /><br />choreograph uses the data of the
          shared databases (hereinafter referred to as “the Data”) to provide a number of marketing
          Services such as prospection, optimization, customer loyalty, e-commerce, ISA etc.
          (hereinafter referred to as “the Services”) for its clients companies. It is specified
          herein that the term "CLIENT" encompass the client company for which choreograph provides
          Services, as well as all and any intermediaries (agents, service providers, agencies,
          etc.), that the client company may appoint to act on its behalf for the performance of its
          obligations under the present General Terms and Conditions of Business. It is understood
          that (i) the client company is fully liable for its intermediaries and shall ensure that
          they comply with the obligations hereunder, (ii) the client company and its intermediaries
          are jointly liable, and (iii) the client company guarantees choreograph in this respect.
          As part of the Services, choreograph provides its CLIENTS with a mix of Data.<br /><br />It
          is specified that since the Services are being carried out on behalf of the CLIENT, the
          latter is responsible for the processing carried out as part of the Services.<br /><br />The
          Data is comprised of transactional data, demographic data, lifestyle data, as well as
          personal data within the meaning of the French Data Protection Act of January 6th 1978 as
          amended by the Act of August 6th 2004 and Regulation No. 2016/679 known as the General
          Regulation on the Protection of Personal Data or "GDPR" (hereinafter jointly referred to
          as the "Data Protection Regulation").</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">2.
          Scope</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">These General Terms and Conditions of Business shall apply
          to any CLIENT wishing to use the Services offered by choreograph. The CLIENT agrees that
          their General Conditions of Purchase shall under no circumstances prevail over
          choreograph’s General Terms and Conditions of Business which the CLIENT is deemed to have
          accepted from the moment choreograph provides the Services<br /><br />The present General
          Terms and Conditions of Business are systematically sent or delivered by choreograph to
          each CLIENT at the same time as the quote submitted in response to its request.<br /><br />Accordingly,
          requesting the right to use one or several database files which belong to choreograph
          implies full and unconditional acceptance by the CLIENT of these General Terms and
          Conditions of Business.<br /><br />Only special provisions specified on a particular
          contract or Specific Conditions agreed in writing between choreograph and the CLIENT may
          deviate from these Terms and Conditions of Business.<br /><br />choreograph's failure to
          object to provisions contained in communications from the CLIENT shall not be construed as
          a waiver of these Terms and Conditions.<br /><br />choreograph reserves the right to
          update or modify these General Terms and Conditions of Business at any time. These
          modifications shall only be applicable to Services performed after communication by any
          appropriate mean of the modified General Terms and Conditions of Business to the CLIENT.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">3.
          Order Process and Validity of the Offer</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">Upon CLIENT's request, choreograph shall send the latter a
          quote or the rates chargeable for its Services. If the Services are chargeable, the
          quotation, or the rates list, lays down choreograph's conditions of intervention for the
          use of the Data requested by the CLIENT as well as their availability<br /><br />The quote
          or the rates offered to the CLIENT will remain valid for a period of thirty (30) calendar
          days from the date it is sent to the CLIENT.<br /><br />The order shall be deemed final
          only upon a written confirmation by a representative of the CLIENT.<br /><br />The term of
          the Services is specified in the quotation. If not specified, the term of the Services may
          not exceed the date on which payment is due, in accordance with article 7.2.<br /><br />The
          Data requested by the CLIENT shall be delivered to the latter by digital medium in
          accordance with the provisions specified in the quote or the purchase order.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">4.
          Obligations of the Parties</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">4.1
          CLIENT's Obligations</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">In the event that a security breach is detected by the
          CLIENT concerning the Data transmitted by choreograph, the CLIENT undertakes to inform
          choreograph of the breach, in writing, as soon as possible.<br />At the end of the
          Services, the CLIENT must permanently delete all Data transmitted by choreograph as well
          as all and any copies that could have been made.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">4.2
          choreograph's Obligations</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">Regarding the Data transmitted to the CLIENT, choreograph
          undertakes and declares that it complies with the Data Protection Regulations.<br />choreograph
          also undertakes to take all its care in the quality of the Services provided and the
          information contained in the Data it makes available to the CLIENT.</div>
      </div>
      <div style="width: 33.33%; padding: 10px;">
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">5. Intellectual Property</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">5.1 Database</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph grants the CLIENT a non-exclusive,
          non-transferable, and personal, right of use on the Data transmitted by choreograph, for
          the term of the Services.<br /><br />The shared databases developed and enriched by
          choreograph are protected by copyright in accordance with articles 112-3, and L341-1 to
          L343-7 of the French Intellectual Property Code, regarding the legal protection of
          databases. choreograph is in this respect the producer of the shared databases.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">5.2 Software</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph certifies that it holds the rights of use or
          property rights in the software used to perform its Services.<br /><br />These General
          Terms and Conditions of Business shall not confer any rights to the CLIENT on the
          aforementioned software.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">6. Data Protection Act ("Informatique et
          Libertés")</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">The CLIENT shall not assign nor transfer to a third party
          the Data provided by choreograph. The CLIENT undertakes not to store nor archive the Data
          on any medium whatsoever beyond the term of the Services or for any other use than those
          agreed between the parties. It is understood that any alleged breach of these provisions
          may constitute a criminal offence for which the CLIENT would then be fully liable.<br /><br />The
          CLIENT undertakes to ensure the security and confidentiality of the Data and, in
          particular, to prevent it from being distorted, damaged, or accessed by unauthorized third
          parties.<br /><br />As a rule, and unless otherwise specifically stipulated, Data are
          intended solely for internal use and for a single use. It can only be transmitted to a
          third party provided that they respect the confidentiality and are able to guarantee the
          integrity and security of the Data entrusted.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">7. Financial Terms</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">7.1 Price</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">The prices of the Services provided by choreograph shall
          be those in effect on the day the CLIENT places its order.<br /><br />The prices specified
          under the confirmation order shall be excluding Value Added Taxes and any other taxes.<br /><br />Prices
          are net and without any discount.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">7.2 Payment Terms and Delays</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">Payment by the CLIENT of the Services shall be due within
          thirty (30) days of the invoice date.<br /><br />The CLIENT shall be liable for late
          payment penalties in case of failure to comply with the payment terms, whether totally or
          partially. The penalties rate will be equal to three times the legal interest rate in
          effect at the time this clause is applied and may be charged ipso jure by choreograph from
          the first day following the due date.<br /><br />In the event of total or partial
          non-payment of more than fifteen days after the due date, choreograph shall have the right
          to suspend ipso jure the delivery of any or all of its Services without any formality
          whatsoever and without prejudice to any remaining sums due and to any other rights and
          remedies.<br /><br />If the Client failed to comply with the payment terms, a fixed
          recovery cost compensation of forty (40 €) euros applies ipso jure.<br /><br />In
          addition, the CLIENT undertakes to reimburse choreograph for all legal, or consulting
          fees, and/or recovery costs, incurred by choreograph to recover unpaid amounts due by the
          CLIENT.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">8. Warranty and Liability</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph is under an obligation to use its best
          endeavors towards the
          CLIENT and does not provide any guarantee, expressed or implied, including
          any guarantee of quality and suitability for a particular use of the Data
          transmitted to the CLIENT by choreograph.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">8.1 Towards the CLIENT</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph cannot be held responsible in the following
          cases:<br /><br />1) In case the CLIENT does not comply with the provisions of the Data
          Protection Regulation;<br /><br />2) When choreograph has formally drawn the CLIENT's
          attention to the existence of potential legal and/or technical risks, which the CLIENT has
          accepted by any appropriate means (email, etc.) in full knowledge of the facts;<br /><br />3)
          When the CLIENT has not complied with its obligations towards third parties or more
          generally its legal obligations;<br /><br />4) When the dispute originates outside the
          French territory.<br /><br />IN ANY CASE, choreograph'S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE
          PROVEN, DIRECT AND CERTAIN DAMAGE SUFFURED BY THE CLIENT WITHIN THE MEANING OF ARTICLE
          1150 OF THE FRENCH CIVIL CODE AND WITHIN THE LIMIT OF THE PRICE OF THE SERVICES AS DEFINED
          IN THE QUOTATION REFERRED TO UNDER ARTICLE 3</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title_2">8.2. Towards third parties</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">8.2.1. Third party complaints <br /> choreograph and the
          CLIENT execute their respective obligations by complying with the principle of loyalty<br /><br />If,
          during the Services, a complaint arises from an individual or a third party concerned by
          the Data, the party to whom the complaint is addressed must immediately inform the other
          party by email confirmed by registered letter with acknowledgement of receipt within seven
          (7) calendar days following the date on which the concerned party became aware of the
          complaint, with regard to the Data Protection Regulation. As such, choreograph has
          developed an internal management procedure to process requests for rights issued directly
          by individuals or through the Data Controller.</div>
      </div>
      <div style="width: 33.33%; padding: 10px;">
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">8.2.2. Breach of Data <br /> If during the Services, one
          of the parties finds that the Data have been or are being brought to the knowledge of
          unauthorized third parties, illegally transmitted, or breached in any way, it must inform
          the other party exhaustively and in writing, of the nature and scope of the incident, and
          of the measures it has taken to urgently stop the illegal transmission and/or unauthorized
          knowledge by third parties, and prevent such occurrence from happening in the future. This
          information must be provided within forty-eight (48) hours from the date on which the
          concerned party becomes aware of the violation itself or the facts suggesting a violation.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">9. Force Majeure</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph cannot be held responsible, or considered as
          having failed hereto, for any delay or non-performance, when the cause of the delay or
          non-performance is due to a case of “Force Majeure” as defined by article 1218 of the
          French Civil Code and subsequent French jurisprudence, including the interruption,
          suspension, reduction and/or power issues or any interruptions of electronic
          communications networks.<br /><br /> The party invoking Force Majeure undertakes to notify
          the other party of the nature and extent of the event by email confirmed by registered
          letter with acknowledgement of receipt, within forty (48) hours of its occurrence and to
          confirm the suspension of the Services as a result. The Services will resume automatically
          and without further formalities upon the disappearance of the cause of the suspension.<br /><br />
          After thirty (30) days following the occurrence of the event and in the absence of
          resumption, each of the Parties will have the option to terminate the Agreement, without
          any compensation being due on both side in this respect</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">10. Transfer of Data</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">All Data are deemed to have been transferred as soon as
          they are received by the CLIENT in their electronic format by means of the secure devices
          offered by choreograph.<br /><br /> The transfer of risks is effective from the date of
          the notification of availability. The notification shall take place by means of a delivery
          note in particular.<br /><br /> The transfer of Data is carried out at the CLIENT's risk</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">11. Bloctel</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">When the CLIENT asks for a delivery of French consumer’s
          telephone numbers requiring a Bloctel processing to be done, it is specified that
          choreograph is only an intermediary between the telephone numbers' service provider and
          the CLIENT. As such, telephone numbers are directly delivered by the provider to the
          CLIENT. Phone numbers do not transit to choreograph, which consequently cannot access them
          nor compare the telephone number database to the opposition list of the Bloctel Service.<br /><br />
          In the event that choreograph is aware of an exception to the obligation to compare the
          telephone database with the opposition list, recognized by the legislation and the
          administrative and/or judicial authorities, it informs the other parties. Any action
          concerning the Bloctel Service has to be done either by the provider or the CLIENT. </div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">12. Operating Retention Clause</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph shall remain free to object to the processing
          of the Data which has been transferred until the full effective payment of the principal
          total amount due, as well as the incidentals.<br /><br /> Default of payment on any due
          date whatsoever may entail a claim for the return of the Data.<br /><br /> This operating
          retention clause shall not prevent the transfer of risk as specified in Article 10.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">13. Confidentiality</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">Both parties undertake to treat as strictly confidential
          all shared information and all documents and information produced under these Terms and
          Conditions of Business or any contracts between them.<br /><br /> The CLIENT agrees not to
          use the Data transmitted by choreograph for purposes other than the performance of its
          obligations arising hereof.<br /><br /> During and after the execution of the Services
          provided by choreograph, each party and its agents undertake not to disclose to any third
          party, without the other party's permission, the methods and tools which are the exclusive
          property of the other Party.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">14. Severability</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">Invalidation of one or more clauses of these General Terms
          and Conditions of Business shall not lead to cancellation of these Terms and Conditions.<br /><br />
          The titles of the articles are given for information only.</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">15. WPP Code of Conduct</div>
        <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">choreograph is a part of the WPP Group and as such
          wishes
          to see its CLIENTS
          respect the rules of the Code of Business Conduct and Social Policy of WPP
          during the performance of the Services. The full text of these codes and
          policies is available on the website www.wpp.com.</div>
        <t t-if="env.user.lang != 'fr_FR'">
          <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">16. Official Language, Applicable Law and
            Jurisdiction</div>
          <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">16.1. Official language<br /> These General Terms and
            Conditions were initially drawn up in the French language and can be provided by
            choreograph upon request. This English translation is provided for information purposes
            only. The French version is the sole legally binding instrument and prevails in case of
            ambiguities or discrepancies.<br /><br /> 16.2. Applicable Law<br /> These General Terms
            and Conditions of Business are subject to the French law.<br /><br /> 16.3. Applicable
            Jurisdiction<br />The Courts of Lille, France, will have sole and exclusive jurisdiction
            in the event of a dispute arising from the interpretation or enforcement of these
            General Terms and Conditions.</div>
        </t>
        <t t-else="">
          <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p_title">16. Applicable law – Attribution of jurisdiction</div>
          <div t-att-style="choreo_style_p">These general conditions of sale are subject to French
            law. <br /> Any dispute arising from these presents or from its execution is within the
            jurisdiction exclusive to the courts of Lille.</div>
        </t>
      </div>
    </div>
  </template>
</odoo>